Uh, fish you could do carpentry with?
(Sheldon:)Why Leonard is such an attractive
and desirable boyfriend?
(Sheldon:)Pick one, your choice.
(Amy:)Sheldon...
(Sheldon:)Did you know that Leonard
has a perfect driving record...
(Sheldon:)...and enjoys the insurance discounts
that go along with that?
Hubba, hubba.
- Okay, go home, crazy man.
- You...
(Sheldon:)Did you know that while Leonard is not
considered a tall fellow in our country...
(Sheldon:)...in today's North Korea,
he's downright average?
(Sheldon:)Talk about a keeper.
(Penny:)Okay, what did Amy tell you?
(Sheldon:)Oh, very well. I can't keep up
this clever charade any longer.
(Sheldon:)She told me that you were thinking
of ending it with Leonard.
Okay, listen to me. It's really sweet
you're trying to protect your friend...
(Penny:)...but this is none of your business.
Got it?
(Howard:)Excuse me,
this is not about protecting my friend.
(Sheldon:)I'm a big fan of homeostasis.